iflyfirstclass.com 2013-05-07

# I Fly First Class. Privacy Policy.

>   
>  Privacy Policy  
> 
> 
> I FLY FIRST CLASS values the users of our website (the Website). Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information (Personal Information) that we collect when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
> 
> ** What Types of Information Does I FLY FIRST CLASS Collect From Me?  
>  **   
>  **Personal Information.** We collect Personal Information that you provide to us, such as your name and email address. **Non-Personal Information.** We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address (Non-Personal Information). Non-Personal Information cannot be easily used to personally identify you.  
>  **  
>  How and When Does I FLY FIRST CLASS Collect This Information?**  
>  **  
>  Providing Information to Us.** We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. If you create your account, we may collect your name, email address, and other information that we request during the registration process. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address.  
>  **  
>  What About Cookies and Web Beacons?  
>  **  
>  A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Website and the I FLY FIRST CLASS Services, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to login and begin use of the I FLY FIRST CLASS Services automatically when you visit the Website.
> 
> A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1? pixel that is placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the Website or receiving the e-mail.
> 
> Cookies and web beacons used by I FLY FIRST CLASS and our online partners are not linked to Personal Information. We have no access to or control over these cookies and web beacons. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and web beacons by I FLY FIRST CLASS and our online partners only and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any other third party.
> 
> **   
>  When Will I FLY FIRST CLASS Disclose My Information to Third Parties?**
> 
> Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties.
> 
> We may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to prevent harm to others, to respond to legal requirements, to protect or enforce our rights and policies, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).  
>  **  
>  Disclosure to Third Party Service Providers and Online Partners.  
>    
>  **We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain and improve the Website and the I FLY FIRST CLASS Services. For example, we use a third party to process payments made to us, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, analytics, reporting or other operations. We also contract with several online partners to help manage, monitor and optimize our Website and the I FLY FIRST CLASS Services and to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information. I FLY FIRST CLASS does not share, rent or trade your Personal Information with third parties for their promotional purposes.  
>  **  
>  Does I FLY FIRST CLASS Protect My Personal Information?**  
>  **  
>  Personal Information.** Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.  
>  **  
>  Tell-A-Friend**  
>    
>  If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about the Website or the I FLY FIRST CLASS Services, we will ask you for your friends name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Website. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.  
>  **  
>  Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Websites?**  
>    
>  You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.
